{
    "id": "8d93ff3872794238b2870b66dbb9b83e",
    "title": "Prepositions Worksheet",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There were ……………… twenty people at the lecture.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "below",
                "under",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8afef8d839ac4e70a40202b7fa4d2f06"
        },
        {
            "question": "She passed the exam ………………….. her teacher.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5aaa9b3434a749a092de992e4507929d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He can’t watch the film because he is still …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "under",
                "below"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "078f792c337042818386936510c7b9aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "The climbers stopped about 200 meters ………………….. the top of the mountain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "under",
                "below",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d0f6997ba3ef4b1897605898ce1de3ad"
        },
        {
            "question": "She went to work ……………… her illness.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "in spite of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0dc7a3a5b03940d28dbb33bc9c6479e3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is writing a book ………………… Hindu philosophy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "over",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d137ea9fc22d4deb9f9cdf64ecc8b583"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is anxious ..................... her health.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a910781ac7dc41a6b718aadcce02a402"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can run 400 meters ………………. about 60 seconds.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "22ffd9a2df1d4a68bd1443ba98ac2fab"
        },
        {
            "question": "They congratulated her ……………… her success.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "with",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "72daf51c77104d89a0400ec4d4357685"
        },
        {
            "question": "My parents never showed if they were disappointed ………………. me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "189e8e18e1a544a1a0eb631b7875ad11"
        }
    ]
}